shoplineapp.com 2019-04-10

# Privacy ｜ SHOPLINE

By joining SHOPLINE as a user, you have entrusted us with an important responsibility and we are committed to upholding a high standard when it comes to our privacy practices and how we deal with your personal information.  
As we value transparency in our practices we have provided a detailed Privacy Policy (the “Privacy Policy”) to explain how we gather, use and protect your information. If you have additional questions, please feel free to send us an email at [hello@shoplineapp.com](mailto:hello@shoplineapp.com)

##### OVERVIEW

The privacy practices of this statement apply to our services available under the domain and subdomains of www.shoplineapp.com (the "Site") and the mobile device application, SHOPLINE, currently available on the Apple iOS App Store, which we own and operate (the “App”) (the Site and the App together, shall hereinafter be referred to as the “SHOPLINE”).  
This Privacy Policy also applies generally to our subsidiaries or joint venture websites (where applicable). By visiting the Site or downloading SHOPLINE you agree to be bound by the terms and conditions of this Privacy Policy.  
If you do not agree please do not use or access our Site.  
This Privacy Policy describes the information, as part of the normal operation of our services; we collect from you and what may happen to that information.  
All of our subsidiaries and joint ventures operate under similar privacy practices as described in this Privacy Policy and, subject to the requirements of applicable law.  
By accepting the Privacy Policy and the SHOPLINE User Agreement upon registration, you expressly consent to our use and disclosure of your personal information in accordance with this Privacy Policy.  
This Privacy Policy is incorporated into and subject to the terms of the User Agreement. 

##### INFORMATION COLLECTED OR RECEIVED

We will not sell or disclose your name, email address or other personal information to third parties without your explicit consent, except as specified in this policy.  
As a SHOPLINE member you may elect to provide a valid email address at registration and choose a username or alias that may represent your identity on SHOPLINE.  
Depending on which services you choose to use, we may require additional information, such as billing address, telephone number, and/or a physical mailing address.  
We may contact individual users to confidentially request more information about their identities or items listed on the site, to ensure compliance with our rules and policies.  
You may optionally choose to provide your full name and other personal information (such as birthday, gender, location) to other users on SHOPLINE in connection to your account and activity.  
Your username or alias is publicly displayed and connected to your SHOPLINE activity.  
Other people may see your date joined, feedback, ratings, profile information, listed items, liked items, followers and comments on SHOPLINE.  
We automatically receive and record some information from your browser when you visit the site, such as your IP address, cookies and data [Anything else we collect on the website or app] about which pages you visit on the site through the use of log files provided by our third-party tracking-utility partners.  
This information helps us analyse and understand how the site works for members and visitors, and provide a more personalised experience for members and visitors.  
Some members or visitors may connect to or register a SHOPLINE account using an external third-party application, such as Facebook.  
We may receive some data from those connected third-party applications.  
Connecting your SHOPLINE account to third-party applications or services is optional.  
We may receive or collect information (e.g. email address) about a person who is not yet a registered SHOPLINE member (a “non-member”) in connection with certain SHOPLINE features, including but not limited to: a non-member subscribing to a SHOPLINE newsletter, a member inviting a non-member to visit the Site or to download the App onto their mobile device, or a non-member engaging in a transaction.  
Non-member information is used only for the purpose for which it was originally submitted to us.  
A non-member can contact SHOPLINE Support if they do not want SHOPLINE to retain any of their information.  
We use the information described in this policy to provide and improve our services, for billing and payments, for identification and authentication purposes, to contact members or interested parties, and for general research and aggregate reporting.  
SHOPLINE’s User Agreement require all account owners to be at least 18 years of age (or have the permission and supervision of a responsible parent or legal guardian), therefore, this policy does not discuss use of our site or services by minors. 

##### SPECIAL NOTE TO CHILDREN

Children (persons under the age of 18) are not eligible to use SHOPLINE unsupervised and we ask that children do not submit any personal information to us. It is our policy not to knowingly solicit or permit children under the age of 18 to provide their personal information for any purpose. If you are under the age of 18, you may only use SHOPLINE in conjunction with and under the supervision of your parents or guardians.

##### CHOICE OF HOW WE USE YOUR INFORMATION

We gives you the choice of providing, editing or removing certain information, as well as choice over how we contact you. You may change or correct your SHOPLINE account information and SHOPLINE profile information (except your username).  
You may remove certain optional information you no longer wish to be publicly visible, such as your full name.  
For various reasons, SHOPLINE may contact you about our services or your activity.  
Some of these messages are required, service-related messages for members.  
Other messages are not required, and you can control which optional messages you choose to receive by contacting SHOPLINE Support via email at [hello@shoplineapp.com](mailto:hello@shoplineapp.com).  
If you have optionally connected your account to an external, third-party application, such as Facebook, you can remove permission for such external third-party application by changing your account settings.  
If you no longer wish to use the services available on SHOPLINE or receive service-related messages, you may close your account by notifying SHOPLINE Support via email at [support@shoplineapp.com](mailto:support@shoplineapp.com). 

##### OUR USE OF YOUR INFORMATION

We use your personal information to facilitate the services you request.  
We use your personal information in the file we maintain about you, and other information we obtain from your current and past activities on SHOPLINE to:  
(i) resolve disputes;  
(ii) troubleshoot problems;  
(iii) help promote safe trading;  
(iv) collect fees owed;  
(v) measure consumer interest in our products and services;  
(vi) inform you about online and offline offers, products, services, and updates;  
(vii) customise your experience;  
(viii) detect and protect us against error, fraud and other criminal activity;  
(ix) enforce our User Agreement; and  
(x) as otherwise described to you at the time of collection.  
At times, we may look across multiple users to identify problems or resolve disputes, and in particular we may examine your personal information to identify users using multiple user IDs or aliases.  
We may compare and review your personal information for errors, omissions and for accuracy.  
You agree that we may use personal information about you to improve our marketing and promotional efforts, to analyse usage of the Site and the App, improve our content and product offerings, and customize the SHOPLINE’s content, layout, and services.  
These uses improve SHOPLINE and better tailor it to meet your needs, so as to provide you with a smooth, efficient, safe and customized experience while using SHOPLINE. 

##### SECURITY

The security of your personal information is important to us.  
SHOPLINE has implemented security measures designed to protect the Personal Information you share with us, including physical, electronic and procedural measures. Among other things, we offer HTTPS secure access to most areas on our Services, and the transmission of sensitive payment information (such as a credit card number) through our designated purchase forms is protected by an industry standard SSL/TLS encrypted connection. We also regularly monitor our systems for possible vulnerabilities and attacks, and regularly seek new ways and Third Party Services for further enhancing the security of our Services and protection of our Visitors’ and Users’ privacy.  
However - while we strive to use commercially acceptable means to protect your personal information, we cannot guarantee its absolute security of your Personal Information, your customers’ information or any other User Content you upload, publish or otherwise share with SHOPLINE or anyone else. No method of transmission over the Internet, or method of electronic storage, is 100% secure.  
We therefore encourage you to set strong passwords for your User Account and User Website. It is important that you protect against unauthorized access of your account and information by choosing your password carefully, and keeping your password and computer secure by signing out after using our services.  
If you have any questions regarding the security of our Services, you are more than welcome to contact us at [info@shoplineapp.com](mailto:info@shoplineapp.com). 

##### DATA RETENTION

We will retain your information for as long as your account is active or as needed to provide you services.  
If you no longer want us to use your information to provide you services, you may close your SHOPLINE account.  
We will retain and use your information as necessary to comply with our legal obligations, resolve disputes, prevent fraud and abuse, enforce our agreements and/or protect our legitimate interests.  
As always, you can contact us to request that we remove your data from our system. We can also help if your customers or visitors ask you to delete data that we store in our system on your behalf. 

##### PRIVACY POLICY CHANGES

We reserve the right to modify this privacy statement at any time, so please review it periodically.  
We’ll communicate changes by posting a notice on the site.  
If we make material changes to this policy you will be notified here, by email, or other places we deem appropriate. 

##### COOKIES

SHOPLINE together with our marketing, analytics and technology partners, uses certain monitoring and tracking technologies (such as cookies, beacons, pixels, tags and scripts). These technologies are used in order to maintain, provide and improve our Services on an ongoing basis, and in order to provide our visitors, our merchants, and their customers with a better experience. The four main functions of these tools are as below: 

  * Site functionality cookies - these cookies allow you to navigate the site and use our features, such as “Add to Cart”.
  * Site analytics cookies - these cookies allow us to measure and analyze how our customers use the site, to improve both its functionality and your shopping experience.
  * Customer preference cookies - when you are browsing or shopping on SHOPLINE, these cookies will remember your preferences (like your language or location), so we can make your shopping experience as seamless as possible, and more personal to you.
  * Targeting or advertising cookies - these cookies are used to deliver ads relevant to you. They also limit the number of times that you see an ad and help us measure the effectiveness of our marketing campaigns.

By using our site, you agree to us placing these sorts of cookies on your device and accessing them when you visit the site in the future. If you want to delete any cookies that are already on your computer, the “help” section in your browser should provide instructions on how to locate the file or directory that stores cookies. Further information about cookies can be found at <https://ico.org.uk/for-organisations/guide-to-pecr/cookies-and-similar-technologies>. Please note that be deleting or disabling future cookies, your user experience may be affected and you might not be able to take advantage of certain functions of our site, and the complete SHOPLINE user experience. 

##### THE EU GENERAL DATA PROTECTION REGULATION

SHOPLINE operates mainly in Hong Kong and Taiwan but we may also serve merchants in the EU. Both Hong Kong and Taiwan is currently not a country in respect of which there is a European Commission decision of adequacy. We are currently working with a team of experts dedicated to making any required adjustments to our products, services and documentation, to ensure compliance with the law in EU. Therefore, we are pleased to reinforce your privacy protection and your rights with the reference of the EU General Data Protection Regulation (EU-GDPR). More information about this is available at [https://www.eugdpr.org](https://www.eugdpr.org/)

##### CONTACT US

If you have questions or suggestions you can contact SHOPLINE’s support team by sending an email to [info@shoplineapp.com](mailto:info@shoplineapp.com).  
If you: 

  * Have any questions or feedback about this policy
  * Would like us to stop using your information
  * Want to exercise any of your rights as set out above, or have a complaint

Please do not hesitate to contact our support team, who will be happy to answer any questions you may have.  
You can contact our team by sending an email to info@shoplineapp.com or through the chat tool at your admin site.
